<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<resources>
    <string name="app_name">Sky Hiking</string>
    <string name="change_name_title">What\'s Your Name?</string>
    <string name="beta_notice">Sky Hiking is still in Beta.\nFound a bug? Please report it at\nhttps://github.com/Nurdok/Sky-Hiking</string>
    <string name="rules1">In Sky Hiking you will join a team of adventurers trying to ride a hot air balloon!\nEach turn, a different player will be the pilot and will have to pay a number of cards determined by a dice roll. The other players will then decide if they leave the balloon for victory points, but the higher you go, so do the prizes get bigger. \nAre you willing to push your luck?\n\nEvery player has a hand of colored cards. The cards are red, purple, yellow, green and "wild", which is marked in white. \nEach round the hot air balloon will start from the first level and get higher with every successful turn. Each turn, the designated pilot will roll a number of dice based on the height of the balloon. Each die contains one side of each color and two blank sides. The pilot will have to pay a card of the same color for each die thrown (unless it\'s blank, of course), or, if he can and wants to, he can pay one wild card for the entire turn. However, before he pays, every player will have to decide if they trust him to have the necessary cards and stay on the balloon or leave and get a number of victory points. After all players have decided, the pilot either pays, in which case the balloon rises to the next level, or, if the pilot can\'t pay (or won\'t play a wild card), the balloon crashed and nobodt on it gets any points! \n\nIn the upper side of the screen, you can see the level meter:\n</string>
    <string name="rules2">\nThe top number is the number of victory points for leaving in this stage, while the bottom number (in parenthesis) is the number of dice thrown. You can see that the last level (25 points) has no dice thrown in it - once you reach it, everyone on the balloon gets 25 points and a new round starts immediately.\n\n\n\n\n\n</string>
    <string name="about">Sky Hiking was created by Amir Rachum.\n\nYou can check out my website at\nhttp://amir.rachum.com.\n\nIf you found a bug, or just want to give me any feedback on this app, you can contact me at amir@rachum.com. I welcome any feedback, even just telling me you enjoy playing!</string>
</resources>